Tori Hart

I have concentrated experience in the field of design and front-end development with focuses on web accessibility, responsive design, UI/UX, SEO. My communication skills, and attention to detail directly contribute to my goal of organizing a web team, managing projects, and training employees and users.

Dearborn Heights, MI (734) 925-2877

torielisehart@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Lead Web Content and Designer, Developer — Henry Ford College, Dearborn, MI

JULY 2017 - PRESENT, DIRECT HIRE

OCTOBER 2014 - JULY 2017, CONTRACTED THROUGH ENERTRON LLC

Front-end Design and Development:

- Created mock-ups and image assets using Adobe Creative Suite.
- Utilized analytics tools to solve usability problems.
- Lead the accessibility conversion of HFC websites.
- Designed, organized content, and developed the main HFC website (https://doi.org/10.1001/journal.2007.0001 and subdomains on Drupal 7+8 CMS platforms.

Project Management:

- Created internal documentation, instructions and guidelines.
- Managed web projects in coordination with Marketing, stakeholders.
- Developed user guides, training materials, and reports to support project implementation.
- Hosted demos, one-on-one training for new feature launches.

Print, Web Designer — Perigee Manufacturing

MAY 2016 - PRESENT

Created branding and product summary brochure. Designed and built the new <u>perigeemfg.com</u> website.

EDUCATION

Technology Management B.S. — Eastern Michigan University, Ypsilani, MI

JANUARY 2017 - APRIL 2018

Web Development Certificate — Henry Ford College, Dearborn, MI

AUGUST 2013 - DECEMBER 2016

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator

HTML5, CSS3, jQuery/ JavaScript

W3C WCAG Accessibility Standards

Drupal 7 and 8 themes, modules

Git, Command Line

ACHIEVEMENTS

Executive Board Member of Local 71 Administrator's Association 2017 - 18

President of Operations Council 2018- 19

Vice President of Operations Council 2017-18

Co-chair of EAB Integration Task Force 2017-18

Member of International Association of Accessibility Professionals (IAAP) 2017-18

HFC Continuous Process Improvement Teams 2015-16